Krishna Jangir

Having experience in front end technologies. Skilled in java script frameworks like ionic and angular. Having knowledge in Html, Css, Git, Json, ES6 and Typescript. Strong professional with Bachelor of Technology in Computer Science from Sobhasaria Engineering College(Sikar).



\times	krishnajj99@gmail.com
9	Gurgaon, India
0	github.com/Krishnajangir

	+91 80949-15483
in	linkedin.com/in/krishna-jangir-997167158

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Senior Engineer

Nagarro

06/2022 - Present

Gurgaon

Associate Technology

Publicis sapient

03/2021 - 06/2022

Gurgaon

Associate Consultant - Frontend

Oodles technologies Private LMT.

10/2019 - 03/2021

Gurgaon

Angular	\bullet \bullet \bullet \circ
JavaScript, Typescript	\bullet \bullet \bullet \circ
Html, CSS, Git	\bullet \bullet \bullet \circ
Bootstrap, Angular Material, Prime	• • • • •
Firebase database	\bullet \bullet \bullet \circ \circ
Node Js, React JS	• • • • •

PROJECTS

Verizon (03/2021 - Present)

- Designing, implementing application with different technologies.
- Code management using github and jira.
- Management with agile scrum and followed all the rules of agile software development.
- We are working on angular 8 version and my responsibility is to enhance site's performance.

Bhaasha (10/2019 - 03/2021)

- Designing, implementing application with different technologies.
- Code management using GitHub and bitbucket, Code review and implementation.
- Created build for apple store and play store for the hybrid applications.
- This project was based on angular JS and ionic 1. And we also migrated the same in angular 9.

LANGUAGES

Interaction with new people

INTERESTS

English

Singing

Full Professional Proficiency

Hindi

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

TRAINING

Industrial Training (23May 2017-07 July 2017) Ducat Institute(Gurgaon)

EDUCATION

B.tech

Sobhasaria Engineering College, Sikar

08/2014 - 06/2018

82.91%

Senior Secondary Sanskar Sr Sec School, Sikar